

MATEUSZ ŚWIĄTEK

STUDENT JUNIOR JAVA DEVELOPER





mswiatek2002@gmail.com



@Mateoswiatek



@Mateoswiatek

SKILLS

Java SQL Python C/C++ Git Linux SpringBoot

PROFILE

I am an ambitious student focused on personal development and acquiring practical knowledge. Currently, I am expanding my experience in Java and SQL(PostgreSQL). I am also familiar with Python and C/C++ (including ROS2). My time in technical school allowed me to gain knowledge in electronics, electrical engineering, PLC programming, and embedded systems, contributing to my success in various Olympiads. I quickly acquire knowledge, which allows me to easily adapt to new environments and improve my skills.

EXPERIENCE

Electronics Intern

PLC programmer Intern

Puch sp. z o.o. • 06/2020 - 07/2020

Aspiring Software Developer

Own projects on Github • 01/2021 - present

Marcontrel sp. z o.o. • 02/2021 - 03/2021

EDUCATION

AGH University of Science and Technology, Kraków

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science and Intelligent Systems 10/2022 - present

Electrical and Electronic Technical School, Szczecin

Technician: Mechatronics 09/2018 - 04/2022

LANGUAGES

Polish - Native English - B2/B1

AWARDS

Laureate of the Olympiad of technical innovations and inventions (OITiW) Ranking, Video

Finalist of the 45th National Olympiad of Electrical and Electronic Knowledge in the mechatronics group (AGH)

I hereby consent to my personal data being processed by Revolut for the purpose of considering my application for the for the position for which I am applying.